callersource.com 2017-09-22

# Privacy Policy

At callersource.com we recognize that privacy of your personal information is extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by and how we use it. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Personal Information Collected**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:  
(a) information about your visits to and use of this website;  
(b) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us and/or using our website features; 

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features.

We also use third party advertisements on callersource.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

**DoubleClick Cookies**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on callersource.com.

Google's use of the cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your prior visits to callersource.com or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Ads Settings.

**Our Advertising Partners**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  
(a) Google Adsense;

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party vendors and ad networks for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This privacy policy document does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Third Party Websites**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
